[Jixiang Unhappy]
[جيشيانغ غير سعيد]
[Episode 1]
[الحلقة 1]
Legend has it that all things have spirits,
تقول الأسطورة أن كل الأشياء لها أرواح،
be it flowers, plants, insects, frogs, or birds and beasts,
سواء كانت زهورًا، أو نباتات، أو حشرات، أو ضفادع، أو طيورًا ووحوشًا،
absorbing the essence of heaven and earth,
وامتصاص جوهر السماء والأرض،
they can transform into human forms.
يمكنهم التحول إلى أشكال بشرية.
Master Jixiang is of the Qilin royal family,
السيد جيشيانغ هو من عائلة كيلين الملكية،
inherently powerful, ruling over all spirits,
قوية بطبيعتها، تسيطر على جميع الأرواح،
revered as the master of myriad spirits.
التبجيل باعتباره سيد أرواح لا تعد ولا تحصى.
Her nature is pure,
طبيعتها نقية
yet her heart is immensely lonely.
ومع ذلك فإن قلبها وحيد للغاية.
Myriad Spirits Pearl,
عدد لا يحصى من الأرواح لؤلؤة,
why am I the only one without friends?
لماذا أنا الوحيد بدون أصدقاء؟
Why is everyone afraid of me?
لماذا الجميع يخافون مني؟
In this world, only you are not afraid of me.
في هذا العالم، أنت فقط لا تخاف مني.
Grant me a friend, okay?
إمنحني صديقاً، حسناً؟
Spirits have a pure and kind nature,
الأرواح لها طبيعة نقية ولطيفة،
coexisting peacefully with humans,
التعايش السلمي مع البشر،
leaving behind many beautiful tales.
تاركا وراءه العديد من الحكايات الجميلة.
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
You've painted it wrong.
لقد رسمتها بشكل خاطئ.
All spirits are evil.
كل الأرواح شريرة.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm Ye Zhou,
أنا يي تشو،
from the Baichuan Sect.
من طائفة بايتشوان.
Baichuan Sect
طائفة بايتشوان.
captures evil spirits to protect the human realm.
يلتقط الأرواح الشريرة لحماية عالم الإنسان.
Are you a spirit hunter?
هل أنت صياد الروح؟
I'm just a humble painter.
أنا مجرد رسام متواضع.
You've got the wrong person.
لقد حصلت على الشخص الخطأ.
I'm searching for a wolf spirit.
أنا أبحث عن روح الذئب.
This is the Spirit Testing Potion.
هذه هي جرعة اختبار الروح.
It's ineffective against humans,
وهو غير فعال ضد البشر،
but once consumed by a spirit,
ولكن بمجرد أن تستهلكها الروح،
it will reveal its true form.
وسوف تكشف عن شكلها الحقيقي.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Okay.
تمام.
Baichuan Sect is quite a bully indeed.
طائفة بايتشوان هي متنمرة حقًا.
Guess you prefer the hard way.
أعتقد أنك تفضل الطريق الصعب.
I'd like to see
أود أن أرى
what kind of creature you are.
أي نوع من المخلوقات أنت.
Making groundless judgments of good and evil,
إصدار أحكام لا أساس لها من الخير والشر،
unable to distinguish between right and wrong.
غير قادر على التمييز بين الصواب والخطأ.
It is you who are the villains.
أنتم من هم الأشرار.
A mere wild dog
مجرد كلب بري
dares to howl at the sky.
يجرؤ على العواء في السماء.
This is truly a lame fight between losers.
هذه حقا معركة عرجاء بين الخاسرين.
Today, I will surely kill you dog spirit.
اليوم، سأقتلك بالتأكيد روح الكلب.
You always cause trouble for me.
أنت دائما تسبب لي المشاكل
Move aside.
تحرك جانبا.
So hot.
حار جدا.
Qilin royal family. Are you perhaps Master Jixiang?
عائلة تشيلين الملكية هل أنت ربما السيد جي شيانغ؟
I'm traveling incognito.
أنا أسافر متخفيًا.
Keep it low-key.
اجعلها منخفضة المستوى.
Scram.
انصرف.
What's going on
ماذا يحدث هنا
with you two?
معك اثنين؟
Don't you know he belongs to me?
ألا تعلم أنه ملك لي؟
I can sense
أستطيع أن أشعر
that the Myriad Spirits Pearl is on him.
أن لؤلؤة الأرواح التي لا تعد ولا تحصى عليه.
I saved your life.
لقد أنقذت حياتك.
That day, I met a god.
في ذلك اليوم التقيت بإله.
From today onward, you are mine.
من اليوم فصاعدا، أنت لي.
But the god said to me...
لكن الله قال لي...
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
I'll come back later and take you to eat something good.
سأعود لاحقًا وآخذك لتأكل شيئًا جيدًا.
Father, I have a friend now.
أبي، لدي صديق الآن.
Where is the Myriad Spirits Pearl?
أين تقع لؤلؤة الأرواح التي لا تعد ولا تحصى؟
It is the spirit pearl born alongside you,
إنها لؤلؤة الروح التي ولدت بجانبك،
the treasure of our tribe.
كنز قبيلتنا.
Come on, don't worry.
هيا، لا تقلق.
I won't lose it anyway.
لن أخسره على أية حال.
[Ten days later]
[بعد عشرة أيام] لن أخسرها على أي حال.
If it's lost, it's lost.
إذا ضاع، فقد ضاع.
With so many powerful elders around,
مع وجود الكثير من كبار السن الأقوياء حولنا،
just casually sending one out
مجرد إرسال واحد عرضا
can help retrieve it.
يمكن أن تساعد في استعادته.
How dare you talk back?
كيف تجرؤ على الرد؟
Losing the Myriad Spirits Pearl will stir up chaos.
سيؤدي فقدان لؤلؤة الأرواح التي لا تعد ولا تحصى إلى إثارة الفوضى.
As a member of the royal family,
كعضو في العائلة المالكة،
you should bear the responsibility.
يجب أن تتحمل المسؤولية.
It's only been ten days since I last saw you,
لقد مرت عشرة أيام فقط منذ آخر مرة رأيتك فيها.
and you've grown so much already.
ولقد كبرت كثيرا بالفعل.
You seem to have forgotten, Young Master,
يبدو أنك نسيت أيها السيد الشاب،
one day in the Spirit Mountain
يوم واحد في جبل الروح
equals one year in the human realm.
يعادل سنة واحدة في عالم الإنسان.
The Spirit King must have mentioned it.
يجب أن يكون الملك الروحي قد ذكر ذلك.
Father has mentioned many things before.
لقد ذكر الأب أشياء كثيرة من قبل.
How can I remember everything he said?
كيف أستطيع أن أتذكر كل ما قاله؟
He looks handsome enough.
انه يبدو وسيم بما فيه الكفاية.
What if there's a mistake?
ماذا لو كان هناك خطأ؟
Get out.
اخرج.
I'm dealing with important matters.
أنا أتعامل مع الأمور الهامة.
The door!
الباب!
So cold.
بارد جدا.
He's freezing.
إنه متجمد.
How strange, I sensed the Myriad Spirits Pearl,
كم هو غريب أنني أحسست بلؤلؤة الأرواح التي لا تعد ولا تحصى،
it's supposed to be on him. Where could it be?
من المفترض أن يكون عليه.  أين يمكن أن يكون؟
His whole body is freezing, luckily he still has a heartbeat.
جسده كله يتجمد، ولحسن الحظ لا يزال لديه نبض في القلب.
Otherwise, he would be like...
وإلا لكان مثله...
A dead person.
شخص ميت.
♪Longing, be it brief or lasting, I always sigh when talking about you♪
♪ الشوق، سواء كان قصيرًا أو دائمًا، أنا دائمًا أتنهد عندما أتحدث عنك ♪
♪Regaining my spirits♪
♪ استعادة معنوياتي ♪
♪He eagerly awaits♪
♪إنه ينتظر بفارغ الصبر♪
♪Embracing them all♪
♪ احتضانهم جميعا ♪
♪When the hibiscus blooms♪
♪ عندما يزهر الكركديه ♪
♪The wind and frost remain♪
♪ تبقى الرياح والصقيع ♪
♪Still hoping for your safe return♪
♪ مازلت أتمنى عودتك بالسلامة ♪
♪Dancing in the sea of flowers in this mortal world♪
♪الرقص في بحر الزهور في هذا العالم الفاني♪
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I saved your life.
لقد أنقذت حياتك.
Is this how you treat your savior?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تعامل بها منقذك؟
I have a body of extreme cold.
جسمي يعاني من البرد الشديد.
Most people, when near me within three chi,
معظم الناس، عندما يكونون بالقرب مني على مسافة ثلاثة تشي،
would shiver all over,
سوف يرتعش في كل مكان،
yet you seem to be fine.
ومع ذلك يبدو أنك بخير.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
I have a body of extreme heat.
لدي جسم يعاني من حرارة شديدة.
Everyone is afraid of me.
الجميع يخافون مني.
I was afraid of burning you.
كنت خائفة من حرقك.
What about that dog spirit?
ماذا عن روح الكلب تلك؟
I scared him away.
لقد أخافته بعيدا.
Don't joke around.
لا تمزح.
This place is dangerous.
هذا المكان خطير.
There may be spirits lurking around.
قد تكون هناك أرواح كامنة حولها.
I felt like I stepped on something and slipped just now.
شعرت وكأنني داس على شيء ما وانزلقت للتو.
Did you see anything?
هل رأيت أي شيء؟
Really?
حقًا؟
I didn't see anything.
لم أرى أي شيء.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I'm going to search for that dog spirit now.
سأبحث عن روح الكلب هذه الآن.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
You took my pearl.
لقد أخذت لؤلؤتي.
Give it back to me.
أعدها الي.
Miss,
يفتقد،
this is our first encounter.
هذا هو لقاءنا الأول.
Why would I take your things?
لماذا سأخذ أغراضك؟
Ten days...
عشرة أيام...
I mean, ten years ago,
أعني، قبل عشر سنوات،
we met each other.
لقد التقينا ببعضنا البعض.
Forget it,
انسى ذلك،
you probably don't remember.
ربما لا تتذكر.
But I really did save your life.
ولكنني حقاً أنقذت حياتك.
What does your thing look like then?
كيف يبدو الشيء الخاص بك بعد ذلك؟
It's about...
يتعلق الأمر...
this...
هذا...
this big.
بهذا الحجم.
It's round and silver-colored.
إنها مستديرة وفضية اللون.
It's very rare and precious in the world.
إنها نادرة جدًا وثمينة في العالم.
Everyone wants it.
الجميع يريد ذلك.
I see.
أرى.
It's getting late,
لقد تأخر الوقت،
you should go back early.
يجب عليك العودة مبكرا.
Don't let your parents worry.
لا تدع والديك تقلق.
Farewell.
وداع.
You returned it so quickly.
لقد أعادتها بهذه السرعة.
Guess you are not bad, after all.
أعتقد أنك لست سيئا، بعد كل شيء.
Cheat!
يغش!
You darn cheat! What I want is the Myriad Spirits Pearl!
أيها الرتق الغش!  ما أريده هو لؤلؤة الأرواح التي لا تعد ولا تحصى!